eximdata.com 2014-05-25

# World Exporters And Importers Trade Directory, Business Yellow Pages.

|  |  | 

|  |  | **1.** | **The Information We Collect**  
---|---  
| 

1.1 

| 

**Publishing Information (Company Information/Free-Listing):** If you submit any information to Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited to be published in any form through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Free-Listing, Add Your Company then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information.   
  
---|---  
| 

1.2 

| 

**Billing & Payment Information:** If you purchase directory, information or any other service from Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited through our website, we or our merchant may collect additional information including billing/shipping information, payment information, delivery options etc.   
  
---|---  
| 

1.3 

| 

Statistical Information: In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions and unique visitors, etc.   
  
---|---  
| 

1.4 

| 

**Communication Services Information:** At the time you use Communication Services (The Services may contain e-mail services, newsletter, tell your friend, feedback and/or other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with us or others) you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business.   
  
---|---  
| 

1.5 

| 

Publishing Information, Billing & Payment Information, Statistical Information and any other information we may collect from you through our any Website or any other means shall collectively be referred to as “Collected Information”.   
  
---|---  
|  | **2.** | **The Information We Don’t Collect**  
---|---  
| 

2.1

| 

**Cookies** : We never use COOKIES to collect/store any information in any form (encrypted/non- encrypted). So you can opt not to accept cookies by modifying the parameter settings on your browser. In the event, your visit to our website will not be affected.   
  
---|---  
| 

2.2

| 

**Credit Card Information:** During Payment through credit card, your payment transaction will process through SECURE PAYMENT GATEWAY. Any credit card information that you provide through our merchant website (CCAvenue.com) is directly submitted to a payment server of the credit card processing bank. Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited does not maintain electronic or physical copies of your credit card information. Read “Privacy of Third Party” for more details mentioned below.   
  
---|---  
|  | **3.** | **How Do We Use Your Information?**  
---|---  
| 

3.1

| 

**General** : We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.   
  
---|---  
| 

3.2

| 

**Publishing Information (Company Information/Free-Listing):** Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited is a business service provider that primarily sale/exchange your company information in various directory format among thousands of potential & interested companies around the world to promote your trade.  
Any Publishing Information that you disclose to us becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us.   
  
---|---  
| 

3.3

| 

**Billing & Payment Information:** The billing & payment information which we collect shall not be disclosed to any third party, other than for legal reasons implied in the transaction. The billing & payment information you voluntarily give us while purchasing on-line is registered. This information is used to process your order and could later be used for further promotional marketing purposes. As part of our marketing policy to advise you of any other offers of related products or services, we may allow other departments of Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited, and the group to which it belongs, to have your name and address and/or email address.  
Any credit card information that you provide through our merchant site (CCAvenue.Com) is directly submitted to a payment server of the credit card processing bank. Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited does not maintain electronic or physical copies of your credit card information. Read “Privacy of Third Party” for more details mentioned below.   
  
---|---  
| 

3.4 

| 

**Statistical Information:** We use Statistical Information to help diagnose problems with and maintain our computer servers, to manage our Site, and to enhance our Site and services based on the usage pattern data we receive. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Statistical Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. We may provide Statistical Information to third parties, but when we do so, we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.   
  
---|---  
| 

3.5

| 

**Communication Services Information:** We may use your Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions.   
  
---|---  
|  | **4.** | **Disclosure of Information**  
---|---  
| 

4.1 

| 

We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.   
  
---|---  
| 

4.2

| 

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.   
  
---|---  
| 

4.3

| 

If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User’s Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited or others.  
  
---|---  
| **5.**|  **Privacy of Third Party**  
---|---  
| 

Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited cannot be held liable for the privacy/confidentiality practices employed by third party to whom we direct our visitors. The privacy policy of such parties may differ from ours, and we may not have any control over the information that you submit to such third parties or co-branded sites. We recommend that you read the confidentiality declaration on each website you visit.   
  
|   
---  
| 

6.1

| 

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.   
  
---|---  
  
6.2

| 

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.   
  
| **7.** | **Changes to Privacy Policy**  
---|---  
| 

We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy from time to time. We recommend that you consult this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited in writing and specifically request that we return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in our possession.   
  
| **8.** | **Your Feedback**  
---|---  
| 

Exim Infotek (India) Private Limited welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses to our email. 

http://www.eximdata.com   

|
